omnivore.com.au 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy – Omnivore

## About

We are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information of our customers (“retailers”) and their customers (“shoppers”) that may pass through our systems. We receive personal information from a variety of sources:

  1. From registration of new retailers signing up to use our software
  2. From marketplaces passing shopper information through to retailers via our software
  3. From third party agencies who are assisting retailers via our software
  4. From requests for help via our Support system
  5. Directly from our website contact form or from email or phone

By using our services you are accepting the terms and conditions of the software and the privacy policy.  Please note that we may update this policy from time to time as required by law or as a result of changes to our services, and you should check back here regularly to make sure you are aware of the current policy.

As part of the normal operation of our business, we may collect the following information on an individual:

  * Name and postal address
  * Email
  * Phone

If the individual is a shopper we will collect the following extra information, for the purposes of conveying a complete order to a retailer for fulfillment:

  * Details of order
  * Payment transaction reference
  * History of previous purchases

Note that **we  do not store or handle** the following information:

  * Bank account details
  * Credit cards
  * Paypal account details
  * Date of birth

## Use of personal information

We retain personal information to facilitate the following:

  1. Creating and tracking orders and purchases made by a shopper for the purpose of fulfilling orders
  2. Resolving customer support issues
  3. Requesting details of our services
  4. The requested addition of extra services to retailers’ subscriptions
  5. To make retailers aware of changes and new features

It is not our practice to communicate with shoppers directly, unless requested to do so by a retailer with whom that shopper has a purchasing relationship.  We will  **never** send material that promotes our services and offerings to shoppers; we believe that the retailer holds that relationship.  We will  **never** sell personal information to any third party.

We may also use  **anonymised, aggregated data** for the purposes of reporting back to the retailer on popular products, patterns of purchasing such as geographical hotspots, price sensitivity analysis and other such general analytics and metrics as required by retailers as part of their day to day operation.  This data is aggregated and stripped of personally identifiable information to give a general overview of shopper behaviour without identifying individuals.

## Storage of personal information

Personal information may be stored in servers located physically in Australia, Singapore and the United States of America and may be copied between these locations as required in the normal operating our our business.  While we make every effort to secure information at rest in our servers using strong encryption and in transit across the internet using industry standard secure transfer protocols, you accept that any personal data you transmit to us is done at your own risk.  Furthermore, if you are a retailer accepting shopper information from us as part of our services, it is **your responsibility** to ensure that this data is held in a secure form and transmitted securely within your own systems.  In addition, you must not disclose your account details such as username and password to anyone, and you must use reasonable efforts to choose a strong password to guard access to our services.

If you no longer wish us to store personal information pertaining to you (if a shopper or retailer) or your customers (if a retailer) then please contact us via the support email and we will remove the data from our systems or anonymise so that individuals can no longer be identified.

## Disclosure of personal information

Shopper personal information will be disclosed to the retailers from whom they have purchased goods or services.  We will pass the above information for the purpose of creating an order in the retailer on behalf of the shopper, as per the personal information given to us by the originating marketplace.  We will retain this information for as long as we deem necessary for history purposes and to facilitate audit trails in the case of disputes and refunds.

Retailer and Shopper personal information may also be made available to partners and contractors of ours for the purpose of facilitating an order transaction, resolving an issue or dispute, providing requested services or as required by law.  We will ensure that they are bound by comparable policy terms as appear in this document.

If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact us to discuss further.
